var questions = 
[
	{ 
		"question": "What is the Capital of Kazahstan?",
		"options": ["Tashkent", "Sucre", "Astana", "Ashgabat"],
		"correct": 2
	 },
	 {
		"question": "Who is the fastest land animal?",
		"options": ["Horse", "Cheetah", "Lion", "Kangaro"],
		"correct": 1
	 },
	 {
		"question": "What is the speed of sound?",
		"options": ["340 m/s", "3.6 km/h", "1020 m/s", "32 m/s"],
		"correct": 0
	 },
	  {
		"question": "Which planet has the most moons?",
		"options": ["Neptune", "Saturn", "Uranus", "Jupiter"],
		"correct": 3
	 },
	 {
		"question": "What is debut studio album by the American rock band Nirvana?",
		"options": ["Come as you are", "Nevermind", "In Utero", "Bleach"],  
		"correct": 3
	 },
	  {
		"question": "What film didn't win 11 Oscar awards?",
		"options": ["The Return of the King ", "Ben-Hur", "Gone With The Wind", "Titanic"],
		"correct": 2
	 },
	  {
		"question": "How many players are in a baseball team?",
		"options": ["7", "11", "9", "10"],
		"correct": 2
	 },
	  {
		"question": "What is the heaviest living reptile?",
		"options": ["Aldabra giant tortoise", "Orinoco crocodile", "Nile crocodile", "Saltwater crocodile"],
		"correct": 3
	 },
	  {
		"question": "During what Chinese dinasty was paper invented?",
		"options": ["Han", "Quin", "Xin", "Ming"],
		"correct": 0
	 },
	  {
		"question": "In which century did Western Roman Empire end?",
		"options": ["5 AD", "4 BC", "7 AD", "6 AD"],
		"correct": 0
	 },
	  {
		"question": "In which century did Francesco Petrarca live?",
		"options": ["11", "12", "13", "14"],
		"correct": 0
	 },
	  {
		"question": "Who was FIFA World Cup winner 1994?",
		"options": ["Germany", "France", "Brasil", "Argentina"],
		"correct": 2
	 },
	   {
		"question": "What is the capital of Bangladesh?",
		"options": ["Hanoi", "Islamabad", "Dhaka", "Kathmandu"],
		"correct": 2
	 },
	  {
		"question": "Where is La Guajira Desert?",
		"options": ["In Columbia", "In Peru", "In Argentina", "In Chile"],
		"correct": 0
	 },
	  {
		"question": "How much world's lakes are in Canada?",
		"options": ["45%", "60%", "80%", "10%"],
		"correct": 1
	 },
	   {
		"question": "Which country has the youngest population in the world",
		"options": ["Niger", "Mali", "Uganda", "Malawi"],
		"correct": 0
	 },
	   {
		"question": "Process that makes organisms better suited to their habitat is called",
		"options": ["Co-evolution", "Speciation", "Co-operation", "Adaptation"],
		"correct": 3
	 },
	  {
		"question": "The amount of energy released when an electron is added to a neutral atom to form a negative ion is called",
		"options": ["Electron affinity", "Electronegativity", "Ionization energy", "Electron configuration"],
		"correct": 0
	 },
	  {
		"question": "When did American Revolution ended?",
		"options": ["1776", "1781", "1783", "1779"],
		"correct": 1
	 },
	   {
		"question": "Who was the drummer of the band The Doors?",
		"options": ["Ray Manzarek", "John Densmore", "Robby Krieger", "Mike Robinson"],
		"correct": 1
	 },
	 {
		"question": "Who was the drummer of the band The Doors?",
		"options": ["Ray Manzarek", "John Densmore", "Robby Krieger", "Mike Robinson"],
		"correct": 1
	 },
	  {
		"question": "Who said 'Happiness is the highest good' ?",
		"options": ["Winston Churchill", "Richard Wayne", "Albert Einstein", " Aristotle"],
		"correct": 3
	 },
	 {
		"question": "Who painted 'Girl with a Pearl Earring'?",
		"options": ["Sandro Botticelli", "Johannes Vermeer", "Gustav Klimt, "Henri Rousseau"],
		"correct": 1
	 },
	  {
		"question": "Which river runs through Paris?",
		"options": ["Rhone", "Loire ", "Garonne", "Seine"],
		"correct": 1
	 }
]